Let's do Cake at Stake!
I really do not like Cake at Stake!
Oh, do you not? I guess we'll take the shortcut and
eliminate you immediately, then.
I really like Cake at Stake.
That's better!
Now we can do Cake at Stake!
♪ Da-da-da-da-da-da ♪
♪ Cake at Stake! ♪
So, the team who lost will do Cake at Stake.
If you remember from last time, good ol' SB ripped the tie.
So, the Grapes won the tiebreaker.
Announcer:
The Cherries lost.
Hee-lo, Cherries!
So, you know the rules:
The one Cherry who doesn't receive cake goes home.
I mean, the TLC if you remember.
Cherries, this is your fourth time here.
Getting used to it?
Just get on with it!
The cake was too expensive, so I got six cupcakes instead.
But think, there are only six.
Anyway, we got thirteen votes.
That's one fewer than last time.
It's the first time it's ever gone down.
[SLOWED DOWN]
I want to cry now. I really do.
Yeah, I don't, like, think so.
ANNOUNCER:
Pin, you have two win tokens.
Would you like to use one now?
Uh, no.
I mean, there's nothing mean I-
Yeah, yeah. We know.
Oh, I just knew you were gonna say that.
'Cause I'm just so smart!
Yeah, not really.
On the test, you scored fourteen out of twenty.
Or seventy percent, which is a C minus.
ERASER:
Ooooh! Burn!
So, here are the seven cherries.
And here are the thirteen votes.
Only one of you got zero votes.
Firey...
Thank you! I needed to hear that!
You are not the person who got zero votes.
Oh my gosh! No fair!
- ANNOUNCER: It's Pencil.
- PENCIL: Yoy!
ANNOUNCER:
Bubble, Firey, and Match; you all got one vote each.
[THROWS CAKES OFF-SCREEN]
ANNOUNCER:
Happy, Match?
I didn't even say the word "a piece."
Ugh! He said it! I'm so, like, not happy!
Cherries, I'll tell you this:
ANNOUNCER:
None of the remaining three of you
got the same number of votes.
Eraser, look!
Pin has to get out! If she doesn't,
one of us is going to the TLC!
You remember how devastating it was
when it was Blocky's time to go!
It can't happen again!
Eraser, the number of votes you got is the
factorial of the difference of the square of the number of
spacial dimensions in this universe,
and one more than the smallest perfect number.
ERASER:
And that is?
Nine. You are eliminated.
Ha ha!
If you were smart, you'd know the result is actually two.
I guess you are not so smart after all!
Grrrr!
Pin, Pen, you are the final two.
And your names sound alike. That's cool.
Cool as Ice Cube because she's frozen!
But Ice Cube, what are you doing here?
You're on the other team!
Ahhhhh!
I have the last cupcake.
Is it for Pen, or for Pin?
Uhm, Mister Speaker Thing?
MATCH:
I see Pen's name written on the cupcake!
Hey! I see mine on mine, too!
[EVERYONE AGREES]
So, does that mean the cupcake's mine and I'm safe?
ANNOUNCER:
Uh, yeah, it does.
That name was not supposed to be there.
So, goodbye, Pin.
I use my win token!
ANNOUNCER:
Too late!
But I'm the team leader! You can't do that!
Oh no!
Eraser, you need a heroic leader like me!
That Pin got what she deserved!
Let that be a lesson:
Use your win tokens before it's too late.
[INTRO PLAYS]
Subtitles: TAFFYMARZI
Look at this!
But in this next contest, teams temporarily
will temporarily be temporarily formed temporarily-
within the teams...
TEMPORARILY.
That's why it's teams in teams!
The Cherries will become two teams of three,
and the Grapes will be three teams of three.
Got that?
Yeah, I guess?
ANNOUNCER:
Our TV will randomly choose teams.
So, Bubble, here's who you will be teamed with.
OM Geez, people! I hope our alliance will be
together as a team!
- Match...
- Yeah!
ANNOUNCER:
And the other one is-
It's, like, so gotta be me!
ANNOUNCER:
Pencil.
Yes! This is, like, a miracle!
So, the remaining Cherries form another team.
ANNOUNCER:
Grape time.
There are nine of you.
ANNOUNCER:
Snowball is grouped with Rocky.
Oh, great! That's helpful!
He doesn't even have arms!
ANNOUNCER:
And Golf Ball.
NOOOOOOO!
- ANNOUNCER: Don't they make a great team?
- NOOOOOOO!
NOOOOOOO!
ANNOUNCER:
The other teams are Leafy, Tennis Ball, and Teardrop.
And Coiny, Ice Cube, and Needle.
So what will you five teams be doing?
It will be three islands.
You will go through all of them in sequence.
Is one of them Dream Island?
Because that would be something I'd really like to-
No. None of the islands are Dream Island.
So, yeah, to start:
Cross that balance beam to get to Island 1.
PENCIL:
We're in first! We're so going to win this!
Look! You weaklings better not make me lose here!
What? You're the only one who matters?
Yeah, duh I am!
Wow, you're stupid.
Woah! I'm the stupid one?!
SNOWBALL:
Yeah you are!
'Cause anyone normal would actually start the race!
Which is what I'm doing!
Come on, Rocky!
Yeah! Let's do this, TD!
Slow and steady!
Out of my way!
Bleh!
Ice Cube! Ice Cube! Where are you?!
Hmm, I'll just get to Island 1 and wait for her there.
That SB is a rager! I hate him!
So, what do we do now?
We'll have to swim to Island 1!
There's no way we could get back on!
Woooah!
Go get GB.
Well, I'll have to plow through all those people!
ANNOUNCER:
No plowing.
Swim back.
If you don't, I'll eliminate you.
SNOWBALL:
Why do I have to do this?!
A team has to stick together. Now go.
SNOWBALL:
Ugh, fine!
Why is he swimming back?
Dunno!
Yeah! I think we're the first team here!
LEAFY:
Woah.
Okay, let's get started!
Push!
Seven, four, nine...
Ugh!
It's a teddy bear.
Where's Ice Cube?
Do you know where she is, Needy?
Don't call me Needy! But, no.
Hey, we're still in second!
We didn't fall too hard behind!
Gosh, GB! I'm here!
Ice Cube! I've been wondering where you were!
Woaaah!
Eraser? Isn't water Firey's poison? He'll die!
ERASER:
Oh! Oh yeah, we'll have to go back and turn on the FRC.
What? A baseball bat?!
Three, six, three!
An egg? What good's an egg?!
Ice Cube, because of what just happened,
I think we need a team leader!
- Can I be-
- NO!
I'll be the team leader!
We must be in last now.
What? It has to warm up?
A flower.
Oh, I don't like Flower. She's mean.
Aww!
Hey, hey! Pretty simple, but that's the raft!
Great, we've got a lead!
Come on guys! I'm here!
Sixty percent done warming up!
Okay, we got it!
TENNIS BALL:
We fell to third!
Is it it? Is it it?
Ugh!
Build! Let's build!
Finally!
ERASER:
Come on, Firey! Don't fall this time!
It's not it again!
Wait, Match!
Gotcha! Whew, this is great!
Snowball! That method of stacking is very unstable-
Shut it!
- That's it!
- Yes!
Let's go!
Oh no! We're the only ones still here!
LEAFY:
Yeah, TD! You got this!
Woooah!
What did I tell you?!
SNOWBALL:
Grrr!
Island 3!
No, it doesn't work! We'll have to go back!
FIREY:
Yeah! Got the raft on the first try!
Let's go!
Hey, you forgot about Pencil!
Let's turn around!
Our key is a fake! It won't unlock!
Let's turn around.
I'm so disappointed!
Snowball, you never learn, do you?
Hey, three teams are still here!
We're still in this!
There's no time to be Mr. Nice Guy!
Oof!
GOLF BALL:
SB, next time, build a stable structure!
So, where's Pencil?
She must be in one of the safes!
BUBBLE:
She's not in this one!
Or this one! Or this one! Or this one!
If we could just climb the pole, we'd be in first!
I'll try!
Oh my gosh, it's slippery!
Okay, I got it!
Pencil! You're here!
Now let's go super fast!
Huurgh... HuuuyYAH!
I think we're still in first!
It doesn't unlock again!
Gotcha!
Go, go, go!
- Yeah, it works!
- Alright!
Hey, it's the Speaker Thing!
Pen, Eraser, Firey, you're the first team to finish.
You each get a win token. Leave.
[EVERYONE SCREAMS]
We're in!
You're team two. Leave.
[EVERYONE SCREAMS]
- Got it!
Paddle fast, fast, fast!
We wouldn't be behind if you two could paddle!
Here we go!
- Team three.
- Yes!
[EVERYONE SCREAMS]
It works!
SNOWBALL:
OUT OF MY WAY!
SB, GB, Rocky, you're team four, so you're all safe. Leave.
[EVERYONE SCREAMS]
Coiny, Icy, Needy-
You're in fifth, last team. One of you will be eliminated.
♪ Coiny, Ice Cube, and Needle: No! No! No! No! No! ♪
Announcer: Viewers out there, vote between Coiny,
Ice Cube, and Needle.
♪ Coiny, Ice Cube, and Needle: No! No! No! No! No! ♪
Wait, we're still flying through the air? Wow, this spring is strong!
LEAFY:
Are we going up or down now?